pokerscout.com 2006-05-03

# PokerScout

|  |   
---|---  
  
|  | 

pokerscout.com Privacy Policy  
  
---|---  

E-mail Privacy Policy  
We have created this e-mail privacy policy to demonstrate our definite commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.  
Why did you receive an e-mail from us?  
If you received a mailing from us,  
(a) your e-mail address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or   
(b) you have registered or otherwise have an existing relationship with us.   
We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.   
How we protect your privacy  
We use the most stringent security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.  
You can be sure that we don't want our customer base (YOU!) accessed by others any more than you want your email address on anyone elses list.  
Sharing and Usage  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.   
How can you stop receiving e-mail from us?  
Each e-mail sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving e-mail from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any e-mail.   
If you have received unwanted, unsolicited e-mail sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that e-mail with your comments to [support@pokerscout.com](mailto:support@pokerscout.com) for review.   
Privacy Policy Changes  
This policy was last updated on January 12, 2003.
